NS VINODH KUMAR

(Account Service Manager)

LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/vinodh-k-592a79152

PROFILE SUMMARY

negotiations & Billings.

I, Vinodh Kumar is an Account Management Expert in B2B sales with 3 years' experience in USA & Indian industries with the skill set of business development and management. Expert in Key Account Management, post-sales, corporate sales, Vendor Management, Quote

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Company: Hourglass Essentials Pvt Ltd

Role: Key Accounts/Accounts Service Manager

Duration: Feb 2020 to Oct 2021

Role & Responsibilities: B2B, Key Account Management, Build and Maintain strong long lasting Client Relationship, Client serving, Business Development, Corporate Sales, Vendor

Management, maintaining ongoing relationship with existing clients, End to End

Management (Inc. Bidding, Follow ups, Providing regular updates on the project, Billing

etc.)

Company : COLIVE

Role : Relationship Manager

Duration : Aug 2019 to Jan 2020

Role & Responsibilities: Interaction with clients, contacting potential clients, closing sales and working with clients through closing process, collaborating with Mgmt. on sales goals, Negotiate and manage agreements through business contract process, ensuring outstanding customer satisfaction by maintaining strong working relationships

Company: Anthem Realty & Investments Pvt Ltd.

Role : Project Coordinator

Duration : June 2018 to Jul 2019

Role & responsibilities: Project Co-ordination, Project Scheduling, maintaining daily weekly and Monthly project reports, Issuing Payroll, Managing Ongoing relationship with clients, QuickBooks (Preparing Invoices, Maintaining Accounts) & payment Follow-ups.

AREAS OF EXPERTISE

Account Management
Relationship Management
Problem Solving
Business Development
Vendor Management
Complex Negotiations

KEY ACHIEVEMENTS

- Won "Best Quality Coordinator reward in 2018" from the hands of Mr. Deepak Chandani President & CEO of Anthem Companies.
- Awarded "NO \$ ERROR" title for maintaining perfect project accounts.
- Achieved Quarterly target and got rewarded Soft Incentive from COLIVE in JAN 2020

SOFTWARE SKILLSET

- Sales Force
- Zoho CRM
- Moxtra
- QuickBooks
- Microsoft Projects (Excel, Power Point & MS word)

ACADEMIC QUALIFICATIONS

Bachelor's in Civil Engineering, SITAMS, Affiliated to JNTU Anantapur, 2018, with 8.71 (CGPA)

LANGUAGES

• English, Tamil, Telugu (Mother Tongue)